Guide to the Washington State Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- WASHINGTON STATE NURSES ASSOCIATION, 1908-1980; RECORD GROUP I
  - ECONOMIC SECURITY PROGRAM RECORDS, SERIES VIII
    - PUBLICITY RECORDS, 1955-1968; SUBSERIES III (Box-folder 7/29-7/43, 33/31-33/32)
      - KIRO radio special report, 1963 (Box-folder 7/40)
      - American Nurses' Association news releases, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 7/41)
      - American Nurses' Association skit: The formation of a local unit, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 7/42)
      - Washington State Nurses' Association Conference skit: The birth of a local unit, 1965 (Box-folder 7/43)
      - News releases, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 33/31)
      - Skits, 1956, undated (Box-folder 33/32)
    - SUBJECT FILES, 1909-1980; SERIES IX (Box-folder 7/44-8/24, 24/1-25/37, 33/33-34/38, 47/27-48/22, 57/24-58/35, 67/26-68/31, 72/33-72/36)
      - Accreditation of Nursing Schools, 1965 (Box-folder 24/1)
      - Advisory council representatives, 1968 (Box-folder 24/2)
      - Air pollution, 1970 (Box-folder 24/3)
      - American Nurses' Association basic speech, 1959 (Box-folder 33/33)
      - American Nurses' Association labor problems, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 33/34)
      - American Nurses' Association news releases, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 24/4)
      - American Nurses' Association news releases, 1968 (Box-folder 24/5)
      - American Nurses' Association orientation, 1968 (Box-folder 7/44)
      - American Nurses' Association sections, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 47/27)
      - American Nurses' Association structure and functions study (part 1 of 4), 1962-1966 (Box-folder 72/33)
      - American Nurses' Association structure and functions study (part 2 of 4), 1962-1966 (Box-folder 73/34)
      - American Nurses' Association structure and functions study (part 3 of 4), 1962-1966 (Box-folder 72/35)
      - American Nurses' Association structure and functions study (part 4 of 4), 1962-1966 (Box-folder 72/36)
      - American Nursing Foundation, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 7/45)
      - Auto and income protection insurance survey, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 58/12)
      - Auxiliary personnel training programs, 1967 (Box-folder 24/6)
      - Board priority lists, 1972 (Box-folder 57/24)
      - Bylaws -- other states, 1967 (Box-folder 24/7)
      - Careers in nursing, article for Guidance Newsletter, 1968 (Box-folder 47/28)
      - Centralized billing, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 33/35)
      - Children's emotional health, 1970 (Box-folder 57/25)
      - Chelan County Tuberculosis League, 1920 (Box-folder 33/36)
      - Commemorative nursing stamp, 1961 (Box-folder 47/29)
      - Committee for Continuing Education Programs in King County, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 67/26)
      - Committee on Coordination of Chronic Illness Services and Research (part 1 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box-folder 47/30)
      - Committee on Coordination of Chronic Illness Services and Research (part 2 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box-folder 47/31)
      - Conference groups, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 47/32)
      - Compensation for part-time nurses, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 7/46)
      - Continuing care project, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 24/8)
      - Continuing education needs of nurses cooperative survey, 1970 (Box-folder 24/9)
      - Continuing nursing education, 1971 (Box-folder 57/26)
      - Continuing nursing education, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 57/27)
      - Continuing nursing education community coordinators, 1971 (Box-folder 57/28)
      - Continuing nursing education credit, 1973 (Box-folder 57/29)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Network project correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 57/30)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Network project correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 57/31)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Coordinator and Recognition Program (part 1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/27)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Coordinator and Recognition Program (part 2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/28)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Coordinator and Recognition Program (part 3 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/29)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Coordinator and Recognition Program, 1977 (Box-folder 67/30)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Coordinator and Recognition Program planning, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 67/31)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Coordinator Program, 1975 (Box-folder 67/32)
      - Continuing Nursing Education Network project: minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 57/32)
      - Courtesy membership and correspondence re graduates, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 7/47)
      - Descriptive anatomical charts, 1959 (Box-folder 33/37)
      - District careers program questionnaire, 1971 (Box-folder 57/33)
      - District program planning ideas, 1964- (Box-folder 7/48)
      - Economic security for nursing association staff, 1958 (Box-folder 47/33)
      - Course in economics, 1963 (Box-folder 33/38)
      - Educators, Administrators, Consultants and Teachers salary survey (part 1 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 24/10)
      - Educators, Administrators, Consultants and Teachers salary survey (part 2 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 24/11)
      - Educators, Administrators, Consultants and Teachers salary survey (part 3 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 24/12)
      - Emergency medical services, 1972 (Box-folder 57/34)
      - Emergency Department Nurses Association, 1974 (Box-folder 67/33)
      - Emergency Services Advisory Task Force, 1974 (Box-folder 67/34)
      - Employment of nursing students, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 7/49)
      - Employment standards brochures, 1958-1964 (Box-folder 24/13)
      - Executive director evaluation materials, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 57/35)
      - Executive order 10988, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 24/14)
      - Extension course in practical nursing, 1951 (Box-folder 7/50)
      - Fifty years of progress, 1908-1958 (Box-folder 7/51)
      - Form letters to graduating nurses, 1959 (Box-folder 7/52)
      - Geriatrics and long-term care resources, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 67/35)
      - Governor's Council on Aging, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 47/34)
      - Guide for the Continuing Nursing Education Coordinator, 1974 (Box-folder 67/36)
      - Headquarters staff employment policies, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 57/36)
      - Headquarters staff job descriptions, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 57/37)
      - Health Care Consortium, 1974 (Box-folder 67/37)
      - Health Care Practice in Remote and Non-remote Sites, 1974 (Box-folder 67/38)
      - Health Care Review Center nursing audit, 1974 (Box-folder 67/39)
      - Health insurance benefits for the aged, 1962 (Box-folder 33/39)
      - Health Manpower Project, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 58/1)
      - Health Manpower Project Advisory Council (part 1 of 2), 1968-1971 (Box-folder 58/2)
      - Health Manpower Project Advisory Council (part 2 of 2), 1968-1971 (Box-folder 58/3)
      - Health Manpower Clearing House program, 1974 (Box-folder 67/40)
      - Home Health Services of King County, 1975 (Box-folder 67/41)
      - Hospital and Medical Facilities Advisory Council, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 47/35)
      - House bill 249, practical nurses, 1947 (Box-folder 33/40)
      - Immunization Task Force, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 67/42)
      - Inactive Nurse Project, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 24/15)
      - Industrial insurance, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58/4)
      - Inservice education guides, 1962 (Box-folder 47/36)
      - Inservice education needs survey responses: hospitals, 1969 (Box-folder 24/16)
      - Inservice education needs survey responses: counties, 1969 (Box-folder 24/17)
      - Inter-disciplinary Continuing Health Education Coordinating Council, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/43)
      - Inter-agency referral form, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 33/41)
      - Journal evaluation, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 33/42)
      - Interstate licensure, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 47/37)
      - Joint employment standards, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 47/38)
      - Joint statements, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 58/5)
      - King County Planning Council. Legislation and Social Policy Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 24/18)
      - Law governing licenses or registration of nurses: pamphlet, 1923-1942 (Box-folder 33/43)
      - Legislation: House Bill 142, 1957 (Box-folder 24/19)
      - Legislative issues publicity, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 33/44)
      - Legislative Action for Women, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 24/20)
      - Licensed practical nurses, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 67/44)
      - Licensed Practical Nurses Act revision, 1966 (Box-folder 33/45)
      - Lillian Patterson's death, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 7/53)
      - Mandatory membership, 1964 (Box-folder 7/54)
      - Manual for district presidents and secretaries, 1954 (Box-folder 33/46)
      - Manual for state committees, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 7/55)
      - MEDEX Program, 1973 (Box-folder 58/6)
      - Medical assistant curriculum, 1964 (Box-folder 47/39)
      - Medical assistant training materials, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 47/40)
      - Membership campaign: correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 7/56)
      - Membership campaign questionnaire, 1964 (Box-folder 7/57)
      - Membership campaign questionnaire, 1965 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Membership film strip narration, 1956 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Membership kit, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Membership Matters newsletter, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - American Nurses' Association membership memos, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - American Nurses' Association membership memos, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - American Nurses' Association membership memos, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Membership application materials, 1970 (Box-folder 24/21)
      - Membership promotion articles, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Membership promotion manuals, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Membership promotion materials, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Membership promotion materials, 1965 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Membership promotion materials, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 24/22)
      - Membership promotion materials, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 24/23)
      - Be-involved membership campaign (part 1 of 2), 1969 (Box-folder 24/24)
      - Be-involved membership campaign (part 2 of 2), 1969 (Box-folder 24/25)
      - Membership promotion: mailing to Schools of Nursing faculty, 1970 (Box-folder 24/26)
      - Membership drive involvement, 1970 (Box-folder 24/27)
      - Membership statistics and dues, 1954-1967 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Membership transfer between states, 1964 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Mental health, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 33/47)
      - Mental retardation, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 33/48)
      - Minority professional nurse survey (part 1 of 3), 1971 (Box-folder 58/7)
      - Minority professional nurse survey (part 2 of 3), 1971 (Box-folder 58/8)
      - Minority professional nurse survey (part 3 of 3), 1971 (Box-folder 58/9)
      - Model form for section and branch rules, 1962 (Box-folder 47/41)
      - Model Nursing Home Program, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 67/45)
      - National Commission for Health Certifying Agencies, 1977 (Box-folder 67/46)
      - National League for Nursing, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 48/1)
      - National League for Nursing, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 68/1)
      - News releases, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 48/2)
      - News releases, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58/10)
      - News releases, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 68/3)
      - American Nurses' Association news releases, 1974 (Box-folder 68/2)
      - District public relations program evaluation, 1972 (Box-folder 58/11)
      - News clippings, 1940-1952 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Nominations for American Nurses' Association sections, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 48/3)
      - American Nurses' Association nominations, 1968 (Box-folder 24/28)
      - American Nurses' Association nominations, 1970 (Box-folder 24/29)
      - An act to regulate the practice of nursing..., undated (Box-folder 33/49)
      - House bill 18, Nurses Bill, 1909 (Box-folder 33/50)
      - Nurse registration, 1933 (Box-folder 33/51)
      - Nurse Practice Act, 1932-1935 (Box-folder 33/52)
      - Nurse inventories, 1949-1965 (Box-folder 33/53)
      - Nurse training program descriptions, 1968 (Box-folder 48/4)
      - Nursing definitions, 1967 (Box-folder 33/54)
      - Nurses in World War II: press clippings (part 1 of 4), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 33/55)
      - Nurses in World War II: press clippings (part 2 of 4), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 34/1)
      - Nurses in World War II: press clippings (part 3 of 4), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 34/2)
      - Nurses in World War II: press clippings (part 4 of 4), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 34/3)
      - Nurses' professional registries, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 34/4)
      - Nursing education, 1931-1947 (Box-folder 34/5)
      - Nursing homes: lists of personnel, 1965 (Box-folder 34/6)
      - Nursing homes: reference, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 34/7)
      - Nursing homes: recommended standards, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 24/30)
      - Nursing in emergency situations continuing education, 1970 (Box-folder 24/31)
      - Nursing practice code of ethics, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 34/8)
      - Nurses' professional registries, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Nursing Service Administrators Section resource material, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 48/5)
      - Nursing service administrators survey, 1964 (Box-folder 24/32)
      - Nursing studies, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 34/9)
      - Nursing surveys, 1950-1964 (Box-folder 34/10)
      - Occupational health nursing (part 1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 24/33)
      - Occupational health nursing (part 2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 24/34)
      - Office nurse employment survey, 1961 (Box-folder 24/35)
      - Olympic College practical nursing program, 1950 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Organization of State Health Functions: report, 1974 (Box-folder 68/4)
      - Payroll deduction procedure, 1969 (Box-folder 48/6)
      - Pearl McIver Public Health Nurse Award, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 24/36)
      - Patient care legal liability: legal opinions, 1945-1964 (Box-folder 34/11)
      - Peace Corps, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 34/12)
      - Portland Regional Inservice Council of Education, 1975 (Box-folder 68/5)
      - Practical nursing, undated (Box-folder 34/13)
      - Practical nursing programs, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 58/13)
      - Practical nursing rules, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 58/14)
      - Practice issues, 1975 (Box-folder 68/6)
      - Private duty membership and salary survey, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 24/37)
      - Private duty nurses: business and occupation taxes, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 58/15)
      - Private duty nurses: income tax issues, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 58/16)
      - Private duty fee records, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 58/17)
      - Private duty nursing needs survey (part 1 of 3), 1969- (Box-folder 24/38)
      - Private duty nursing needs survey (part 2 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 25/1)
      - Private duty nursing needs survey (part 3 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 25/2)
      - Private Duty Section responsibility slips, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 25/3)
      - Private Duty Section standards, 1953-1965 (Box-folder 48/7)
      - Professional Credentials and Personnel Service, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 25/4)
      - Professional Nurse Day, 1963 (Box-folder 48/8)
      - Professional Nurse Day, 1964 (Box-folder 48/9)
      - Professional Nurse Day photographs, 1965 (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Professional Nurse Week: work file, 1965 (Box-folder 34/14)
      - Professional Nurse Week: publicity, 1965 (Box-folder 34/15)
      - Professional Nurse Week: news clippings, 1965 (Box-folder 34/16)
      - Professional Nurse Week: questionnaire, 1965 (Box-folder 34/17)
      - Professional Nurse Week: correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 34/18)
      - Professional Nurse Week: materials and reports, 1966 (Box-folder 34/19)
      - Professional Nurse Week: manual copy, 1966 (Box-folder 34/20)
      - Professional Nurse Week: correspondence re materials, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 25/5)
      - Professional Nurse Week, 1968 (Box-folder 25/6)
      - Professional Nurse Week: news clippings, 1968 (Box-folder 25/7)
      - Professional Nurse Week: photographs, 1968 (Box-folder 25/8)
      - Professional Nurse Week: correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 25/9)
      - Professional Nurse Week: manual copy, 1970 (Box-folder 25/10)
      - Professional Nurse Week: reports on results (part 1 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 25/11)
      - Professional Nurse Week: reports on results (part 2 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 25/12)
      - Professional Nurse Week evaluation, 1971 (Box-folder 25/13)
      - Professional Nurse Week: news clippings, 1970 (Box-folder 25/14)
      - Professional Nurse Week: photographs, 1970 (Box-folder 25/15)
      - Professional Nurse Week public relations, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 58/18)
      - Professional Nurse Week, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 58/19)
      - Professional Nurse Week press clippings, 1972 (Box-folder 58/20)
      - Professional Nurse Week: District 6, 1972 (Box-folder 58/21)
      - Professional nursing practice statement with Physical Therapists Association, 1967 (Box-folder 25/16)
      - Professional registry, 1954-1970 (Box-folder 58/22)
      - Professional registry quarterly report: District 2, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 58/23)
      - Professional Standards Review Organization, 1973 (Box-folder 58/24)
      - Professional Review Standards Organization, 1975 (Box-folder 68/7)
      - Proposed changes to Minimum Wage Order No. 46. Public housekeeping -- women and minors: public hearing transcript volume I, 1961 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Proposed changes to Minimum Wage Order No. 46. Public housekeeping -- women and minors: public hearing transcript volume II, 1961 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Proposed revision of nurse practice acts, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Psychiatric Nursing Study Group, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Psychiatric nursing, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 34/21)
      - Public health economic security, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 25/17)
      - Public health nursing consultants (part 1 of 3), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 25/18)
      - Public health nursing consultants (part 2 of 3), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 25/19)
      - Public health nursing consultants (part 3 of 3), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 25/20)
      - Public relations, 1953-1960 (Box-folder 34/22)
      - Public relations, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 34/23)
      - Public relations reference materials, 1949-1959 (Box-folder 48/11)
      - Public relations reference materials, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 48/12)
      - Seattle newspapers' annual medical sections, 1950 (Box-folder 34/24)
      - Press clippings, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 34/25)
      - News releases, 1941 (Box-folder 34/26)
      - Public relations, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 25/21)
      - Public relations: news releases, 1967 (Box-folder 25/22)
      - Public relations: news releases, 1968 (Box-folder 25/23)
      - Public relations: news releases, 1969 (Box-folder 25/24)
      - Public relations: news releases, 1970 (Box-folder 25/25)
      - Public relations program evaluation (part 1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 25/26)
      - Public relations program evaluation (part 2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 25/27)
      - Puget Sound Health Planning Council, 1975 (Box-folder 68/8)
      - Questionnaires and surveys, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 25/28)
      - Refresher course curricula, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 58/25)
      - Registered nurses in nursing homes, 1963 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Registered nurses licensing fee, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 68/9)
      - Resident registered nurse program in hospitals, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 68/10)
      - Review of economic security program, 1957 (Box-folder 34/27)
      - Records retention, 1968 (Box-folder 34/28)
      - Research project in pediatric assistance, 1968 (Box-folder 34/29)
      - Rural health project and conference, 1975 (Box-folder 68/11)
      - School nurse reference materials, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 48/13)
      - School Nurses of Washington (SNOW), 1967 (Box-folder 34/30)
      - School nurses, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 25/29)
      - Skilled nursing care, 1974 (Box-folder 68/12)
      - Standards for certification of school nurses, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 48/14)
      - State Board Test Pool Examination, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 34/31)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students: correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 25/30)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students: work done for, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 25/31)
      - Structure and Services survey questionnaire responses, 1976 (Box-folder 68/13)
      - Student essays "why I like nursing", 1950-1951 (Box-folder 34/32)
      - Survey of non-professional hospital workers in Washington, 1940 (Box-folder 34/33)
      - Survey of salaries of employees of state nursing associations, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 25/32)
      - Survey on mixed boards of nursing, 1961 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Survey on temporary permits for nurses to work, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Task Force questionnaire, 1968 (Box-folder 58/26)
      - Task Force survey, 1971 (Box-folder 58/27)
      - Tri-state Continuing Nursing Education Workshop planning, 1975 (Box-folder 68/14)
      - U.S. Fair Labor Standards Act, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 34/34)
      - U.S. military nurses, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 34/35)
      - University of Washington School of Nursing faculty, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 34/36)
      - Visiting Nurse Service, 1965 (Box-folder 34/37)
      - Washington/Alaska Regional Medical Program, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 68/15)
      - Washington Association for Social Welfare, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 48/15)
      - Washington Association for Social Welfare, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 48/16)
      - Washington State Board for Community College Education, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 25/33)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 58/28)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing annual report, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 48/17)
      - Washington State boards and commissions, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 68/16)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 68/17)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board, 1977 (Box-folder 68/18)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board (part 1 of 3), 1978 (Box-folder 68/19)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board (part 2 of 3), 1978 (Box-folder 68/20)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board (part 3 of 3), 1978 (Box-folder 68/21)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board: minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 68/22)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board: minutes, 1976 (Box-folder 68/23)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board: minutes, 1977 (Box-folder 68/24)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board: minutes, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 68/25)
      - Washington State Employees Insurance Board: WAC rules, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 68/26)
      - Washington State Hospital Association (part 1 of 3), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 48/18)
      - Washington State Hospital Association (part 2 of 3), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 48/19)
      - Washington State Hospital Association (part 3 of 3), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 48/20)
      - Washington State Hospital Association, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 58/29)
      - Washington State Hospital Commission, 1975 (Box-folder 68/27)
      - Washington State Hospital Education and Research Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 58/30)
      - Washington State League for Nursing, 1967 (Box-folder 34/38)
      - Washington State League for Nursing, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 68/28)
      - Washington State legislation, 1963 (Box-folder 48/21)
      - Washington State legislation, 1965 (Box-folder 48/22)
      - Washington State Inter-agency Committee on Staphylococcal Infections, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Washington State. Interim Committee on Collective Bargaining, 1969 (Box-folder 25/34)
      - Washington State. Governor's Medical Advisory Committee, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 25/35)